<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-04-05T17:35:50+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/feed.xml</id><title type="html">(VeronicaBlog)</title><subtitle>This is the place where I talk about stuff that's too meta for Insta.</subtitle><author><name>Veronica Cheung</name></author><entry><title type="html">ENTP or ENFP Vol.1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/jekyll/update/2020/04/05/ENTP-or-ENFP-Vol-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="ENTP or ENFP Vol.1" /><published>2020-04-05T00:16:00+08:00</published><updated>2020-04-05T00:16:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/jekyll/update/2020/04/05/ENTP-or-ENFP-Vol-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/jekyll/update/2020/04/05/ENTP-or-ENFP-Vol-1.html"></content><author><name>Veronica Cheung</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">bundle exec jekyll serve</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/jekyll/update/2020/04/04/bundle-exec-jekyll-serve.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="bundle exec jekyll serve" /><published>2020-04-04T13:10:09+08:00</published><updated>2020-04-04T13:10:09+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/jekyll/update/2020/04/04/bundle-exec-jekyll-serve</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/jekyll/update/2020/04/04/bundle-exec-jekyll-serve.html">&lt;p&gt;I can't figure out stupid Github pages. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually, I'm the stupid one. I've been trying to figure out this for so long, I don't even know if this is &quot;worth it&quot; haha. I haven't even finished my IES. I guess I'll just stay here and I dunno, work all day again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, I asked on StackOverflow, and I hope some middle-aged white dude will answer my question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, things to work as well as you want them to be, but you just gotta accept it and hustle. That is something I've learned after 3-4 years of dabbling in coding, I guess. When I can't seem to figure out this ONE particular problem in my site, the final solution (well not final but, a desperate choice nonetheless) I have is to ask the Internet. And the Internet is full of white tech dudebros. In fact, a French possibly dudebro gave me a potential solution to my StackOverflow question but, I think I am way too proud to try his solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is also something I've been trying to work on. Sometimes I find myself too humble/ awkward with people. We used to idolize the higher form students at our school, but now when we are the juniors and seniors, we don't feel a particular sense of superiority. That might be due to the fact that kids nowadays are meaner/ more disrespectful, but I would have loved to feel that kind of 'I am older therefore I'm wiser' kind of mood. Now, when I give suggestions to reporters as the sub-editor of our school magazine, I would put 'haha's, 'lol's and 'i guess' after my constructive criticisms, to lighten the mood and to make my comment less mean. That is totally not necessary but, I'm awkward in that kind of way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other times, I am egotistic. I am too proud and pretentious. I used to post videos that I am proud of to Instagram/ Facebook and now I look back it is just the highest purest form of cringe. We all do embarrassing things when we were young, but sometimes I get a sense of entitlement from myself. Like 'I think I am cooler than you, so I am posting this to prove that'. Same goes to the Spotify screenshots and Netflix-tilted-what-I-am-watching stories. I don't want to look like a show-off, I don't think I am trying to be one, but it comes off as a pretentious douchebag move. I don't want to be judged in this way. And this goes BACK to my 'too awkward' problem. On one hand, I should not care what other people think about my posts. 'I am not trying to be pretentious here. If you don't like my stuff, you can leave.' and 'I am sorry to bother you, is this stupid? I am trying too hard to be edgy.' The eternal dilemma haunts me every time I post something to my Instagram stories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, if any dudebro answers my noob question on StackOverflow, I will politely thank him but at the same time despise him for being smarter than me. It's almost like I am a hybrid of Hufflepuff and Slytherin.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Veronica Cheung</name></author><summary type="html">I can't figure out stupid Github pages.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">First Things First</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/blog/2020/04/03/first-things-first.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="First Things First" /><published>2020-04-03T12:58:09+08:00</published><updated>2020-04-03T12:58:09+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/blog/2020/04/03/first-things-first</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/blog/2020/04/03/first-things-first.html">&lt;p&gt;I hope I can somehow “inspire” you to do stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically, one of my goals this break is to not let one part of myself define my entire being. What I mean by that is I don’t want to display just one interest/ hobby/ personality of mine define lolurnotveronica. I like music, I like films, I like my turtles, but I’m much more than that. I think one of the main problems with social media (there are a LOT of problems) is that people tend to define themselves to one certain aspect. like your appearance, your sports team, your school stuff, your food and your travels. I don’t know how to fix that, cuz deep down all we want is to display the best part of ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But there is no “best part of ourselves”. There are a hundred layers to a person. And it is hard to display all of that in one, instagram story. The worst part is, we don’t want others to know the ugly parts of ourselves. so when people post stuff about themselves, they only post the cool stuff to make ppl like them. That is completely fine, like we would do that already social media or not. The problem is, it creates an illusory persona that might make us feel like we need to live ‘up’ to that standard. For example, photoshopping yourself makes you look cooler. But if you photoshop every single picture of yourself, it makes you think that people would only like you if you look like your photoshop self. Truth is, you will never be satisfied. The person in that picture is no longer ‘you’. That, my friend, is the ‘you’ you want people to look at, to believe that is you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why am I bringing this up? Because I want to start this blog/ online journal thing to start sharing other part of lolurnotveronica. A part that, still, would be semi-idealistic and too-cool-for-instagram, but at least I can share something. I wanna talk about things that are not always displayed through Instagram stories, parts of me that I want to share but might come off as ‘pretentious’ and annoying just to spam everyone. This is like a glimpse of my brain and opinions that I’ve always wanted to share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not ‘the best part of myself’. But it certainly is one part of lolurnotveronica. I don’t have perfect grammar or perfect writing styles, but I think you don’t need that to share things effectively. Actually you do but, whatever I have Grammarly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I might also do some movie reviews, fav book of the week, spotify playlist etc. All kinds of pretentious stuff that I feel uncomfortable doing on Instagram stories. You can't judge the content here, right? This is literally my show.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Veronica Cheung</name></author><summary type="html">I hope I can somehow “inspire” you to do stuff.</summary></entry></feed>